A Finding Aid to the Holly Solomon Gallery Records, circa 1948-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.hollsolg
Archives of American Art
- Subject Files, circa 1975-2002; Series 3; (Boxes 11-25; 15.0 linear feet)
  - Europe-Christo/Picasso Trip, September 1985 (Box 15)
  - Everson Museum, 1987-1991 (Box 15)
  - Exhibitions of Private Collection, 1976-1985 (Box 15)
  - Fahey-Klein, 1987-1991 (Box 15)
  - Rosamund Felson Gallery, circa 1980s (Box 15)
  - FIAC, 1990-2000; (7 folders) (Box 15)
  - FIAC Shipping Form, 1991 (Box 15)
  - Film, 1998 (Box 15)
  - Fine Arts Service, 1985-1992 (Box 15)
  - First New York Bank for Business, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Flatware, undated (Box 15)
  - Fontana, 1989-1997 (Box 15)
  - Galleria Fonte D'Abisso, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Fort Lauderdale Museum, 1991-1993 (Box 15)
  - Forest, Fred, 1996 (Box 15)
  - Fortress Fae, 1999 (Box 15)
  - Jean Fornier, 1987-1994 (Box 15)
  - David Frankel Realty, 1989-1992 (Box 15)
  - Fraenkel Gallery, 1983-1990 (Box 15)
  - E. Frank Gallery, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Frankfurter Kunstvereins, 1985-1990 (Box 15)
  - Nina Freudenheim, 1983-1990 (Box 15)
  - Fujii Gallery, 1984-1992 (Box 16)
  - Fuller Goldeen Gallery, 1983-1988 (Box 16)
  - N. Gabo, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Gaynes, Phil and Sue, 1979-1992 (Box 16)
  - Geneva Museum, 1981-1984 (Box 16)
  - Romeo Gigli, 1989-1996; (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Galerie Gillespie de Laage, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Fay Gold Gallery, 1987-1991 (Box 16)
  - Joan Goldberg, 1986-1988 (Box 16)
  - Mara Goldberg, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Gorky, 1989 (Box 16)
  - Gracie Mansion, 1985-1997 (Box 16)
  - Gramercy Art Fair, 1996-1998; (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Graphic Design - Rates and Samples, undated (Box 16)
  - [Greenberg Gallery], 1982-1985 (Box 16)
  - Greene Gallery, 1988-1991 (Box 16)
  - Nigel Greenwood, 1985-1990; (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Greenville County Museum, 1985-1988 (Box 16)
  - Grey Art Gallery, 1982-1985 (Box 16)
  - [Michail Grobman], 1990 (Box 16)
  - Groninger, 1984-1996; (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Group Shows, 1996-1997 (Box 16)
  - Galerie Tania Grunert, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Guggenheim, 1996-2002; (4 folders) (Box 16)
  - Michel Haas, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Hankes, Claude, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
  - Heiga, 1998 (Box 17)
  - Sonja Henie Art Center, 1992-1996 (Box 17)
  - Hepworth, undated (Box 17)
  - Hessel, Marlies, 1979-1985 (Box 17)
  - High Museum, 1982-1993 (Box 17)
  - Hill, Lee, 1990 (Box 17)
  - Hillberry Gallery, 1981-1992 (Box 17)
  - Hirshhorn Museum, 1980-1996 (Box 17)
  - Rhona Hoffman Gallery, 1985-1996 (Box 17)
  - Holland, undated (Box 17)
  - Holly Solomon Editions, 1980-1986; (See box 23) (Box 17)
  - Jackie Holmes, 1992-1993 (Box 17)
  - Hornick, 1985-1988 (Box 17)
  - Horst, 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Houston Museum of Fine Art, 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Pierre Huber, 1990-1993 (Box 17)
  - Hudson River Museum, 1983-1989 (Box 17)
  - Donald Hutter, 1986-1992 (Box 17)
  - IBJ, 1999 (Box 17)
  - IBJ Schoeder Bank, 1981-1998 (Box 17)
  - ICA, Boston, 1986-1991 (Box 17)
  - ICA, [London], 1982-1994 (Box 17)
  - Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1984-1997 (Box 17)
  - Internet Auction, 1999 (Box 17)
  - Internship Resumes, 1990 (Box 17)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art (University of Pennsylvania), 1983-1991 (Box 17)
  - [Tom Ireland], 1983-1993 (Box 17)
  - [Tom Ireland], 1983-1993 (Box 18)
  - Isetan, 1990-1991; (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Friends of Isreal Museum, 1984-1988 (Box 18)
  - Italians, circa 1975-2000 (Box 18)
  - Italy, 1990-1992 (Box 18)
  - Japan, 1986 (Box 18)
  - Japan - Paper Works Exhibition, 1986-1995 (Box 18)
  - Japanese Galleries, 1997 (Box 18)
  - Jewish Museum, 1989-1998 (Box 18)
  - Kampl, Gudrun, circa 1990s (Box 18)
  - Robert Kardon, 1984-1990 (Box 18)
  - Aron and Phylis Katz, 1982-1988 (Box 18)
  - R. M. Kaye, 1985-1989 (Box 18)
  - Keitelmen, Maurice, 1990-1996 (Box 18)
  - Kestner-Gesellschaft, 1984-1988 (Box 18)
  - Kitaryushu Municipal Museum of Art, 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - Bernd Kluser, 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - KLM to Paris, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Knight Gallery (Shengold/Pfaff), 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Koegel - att Warhol, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Korean Museums, 1986-1992 (Box 18)
  - Barbara Krakow, 1985-1988 (Box 18)
  - Hilton Kramer, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Ms. Ursula Krinzinger, 1982-1991 (Box 18)
  - Krugier, 1983-1992 (Box 18)
  - Kunsthalle New York Project - Martin Kunz, Director, 1990-1997 (Box 18)
  - Kunsthaus Zurich, 1990-1992 (Box 18)
  - Kunstmusuem Bern, 1997 (Box 18)
  - Kunstmusuem Luzern, 1986-1992 (Box 18)
  - Art LA, 1988 (Box 18)
  - L.A. County Musuem, 1987-1991 (Box 18)
  - Paul LaBell, 1991 (Box 18)
  - LaForet Museum, 1984-1991 (Box 18)
  - Langer Fain, 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Sarah Lawrence College, 1982-1990 (Box 19)
  - [Evelyn Lauder], 1992-1994; (3 folders; See also box 33) (Box 19)
  - Lauder Sales Information, 1992-1993 (Box 19)
  - Lengendary Women, 1998 (Box 19)
  - Margo Leavin, 1978-1988 (Box 19)
  - Richard Levine, 1978-1992 (Box 19)
  - LeWitt, Sol, 1996 (Box 19)
  - Lindfors, 1996 (Box 19)
  - Loeber Landau, 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - London, 1989 (Box 19)
  - London Art Fair, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Lowe Museum, Miami, 1979-1987 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Peter Ludwig, 1978-1993; (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Gloria Luria Gallery, 1984-1990 (Box 19)
  - Luscher, 1997 (Box 19)
  - Paul Maenz, 1987-1988 (Box 19)
  - Galerie Mai 36, 1988-1993 (Box 19)
  - Donato Maino, 1985-1989 (Box 19)
  - Anders Malmberg, 1978-1992; (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Allison Mann, 1991-1992 (Box 19)
  - Mannheim Kunstverein, 1979-1980; (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Studio Marconi, 1982-1987; (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - University of Massachusetts at Amherst, 1985-1990 (Box 20)
  - Hans Mayer, 1984-1993 (Box 20)
  - The Mayor Gallery, 1980-1996; (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Menzel, Silvia, 1999 (Box 20)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1983-1999 (Box 20)
  - Metropolitan Home Diffa, 1988; (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Middendorf Gallery, 1984-1993 (Box 20)
  - Milwaukee Art Museum (Russell Bowman), 1986-1995 (Box 20)
  - Jay Milligan, 1991 (Box 20)
  - Zairra Mis, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Moody Gallery, 1982-1989 (Box 20)
  - Juana Mordo, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Museum Masters International, 1998 (Box 20)
  - Musuem of Modern Art [MOMA], 1984-2000; (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - MOMA Art Advisory, 1990-1999 (Box 21)
  - Museum of Modern Art, Denmark, 1995-1996 (Box 21)
  - Museum Fur Kunsthandwerk, Frankfort, 1990 (Box 21)
  - Musee d'Art Contemprain de Montreal, 1984-1989 (Box 21)
  - National Museum of Woman in the Arts, 1988-1994 (Box 21)
  - Nauman, Bruce, circa 1980s (Box 21)
  - Neko, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Neuberger Museum, 1982-1992 (Box 21)
  - Neuman, Morton, 1983 (Box 21)
  - The New Yorker, 1997 (Box 21)
  - The New York Times, 1999 (Box 21)
  - Newark Museum, 1990 (Box 21)
  - New Jersey Performing Arts, 1999 (Box 21)
  - New School and New Museum, 1983-1999 (Box 21)
  - New York University, 1990-1998 (Box 21)
  - Nezhat, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Noguchi, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Galerie Oz, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Paper Magazine, 1999 (Box 21)
  - "Legal Eagles" [Pace/MacGill Gallery], 1986-1993 (Box 21)
  - Paris, 1987-1990 (Box 21)
  - Paris-FIAC, 1977-1978; (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - Patkin Notes, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Pauley Glass, 1991-1992 (Box 21)
  - Persons Gallery, undated (Box 21)
  - PS1 [Project Studio 1], 1983-1987 (Box 21)
  - PSG Framing, 1985-1993; (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Philadelphia, 1983-1994 (Box 22)
  - Phoenix Art Musuem, 1983-1992 (Box 22)
  - Photographers, undated (Box 22)
  - "Pineapple" [Gallery Leasing Information], 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Polaroid, 1985-1988 (Box 22)
  - Primo Piano, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - (Princeton University) The Art Museum, 1985-1991 (Box 22)
  - Prudential, 1982-1988 (Box 22)
  - Leslie Rankow, 1989-1990 (Box 22)
  - Rheinisches Landesmuseum, Bonn, 1981-1986; (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Reiff, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Republic Hogg Robinson, 1989-1992 (Box 22)
  - Renoir, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Frederick Roos, 1979-1997 (Box 22)
  - Ringling Musuem of Art, 1985-1995 (Box 22)
  - Ruffner, 1986, 1994-1995 (Box 22)
  - Salama-Caro, 1990-1995; (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Saatchi, 1979-1994 (Box 22)
  - Schloss '99, 1999 (Box 22)
  - Seattle Art Museum, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Sidley-Austin, 1989-1993 (Box 22)
  - [Beverly Semmes], 1994 (Box 22)
  - Slonem, Alina, 1993 (Box 22)
  - Holly Solomon Editions, 1980-1986; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Tom Solomon's Garage, 1990-1997; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Carl Solway, 1987-1993 (Box 23)
  - Sonje Museum, Korea, 1993 (Box 23)
  - [Earl Staley], 1988 (Box 23)
  - St. Etienne, 1988-1989 (Box 23)
  - St. Louis Art Museum, 1985-1992 (Box 23)
  - Lynn Stacher, 1989-1992 (Box 23)
  - Starkman, 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - Stedelijk Museum, 1985-1993 (Box 23)
  - Stern, Peter, 1986-1990 (Box 23)
  - Stettheimer, 1985-1995 (Box 23)
  - Stikas, Marianne, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Storm King Art Center, 1991-1997 (Box 23)
  - Galerie Swart, Amsterdam, 1985-1993 (Box 23)
  - Swedish Artists, circa 1996 (Box 23)
  - Szeeman, Harald, 1982-1998 (Box 23)
  - Team Productions, 1988 (Box 23)
  - P.N. Teplitz, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Teutloff, Lutz, 1996 (Box 23)
  - Texas Gallery, 1981-1992; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - [Danielle Tilkin], 1990 (Box 24)
  - Trapp Associates, 1983-1992 (Box 24)
  - Tuttle, 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - Twigg-Smith, 1985-1999; (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Usdan Center for the Creative and Performing Arts, 1983-1998; (3 folders) (Box 24)
  - Valencia, Matta-Clark, 1991-1993; (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Vermillion, 1986-1992; (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Venice Biennale, 1984-1990 (Box 24)
  - Venice Biennale, 1984-1990 (Box 25)
  - Viart, 1984-2000; (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Village Voice, 1983-1986 (Box 25)
  - Walker Art Center, 1982-1998 (Box 25)
  - Weinberg Gallery, 1981-1989 (Box 25)
  - Whitney Museum, 1983-1996; (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Washington, DC Art Fair, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
  - Donald Roller Wilson-Correspondence, 1982-1992; (3 folders) (Box 25)
  - Galerie Susan Wyss, 1990-1991 (Box 25)
  - Yaddo, 1999 (Box 25)
  - Yarber, Robert, 1988 (Box 25)
  - Souyun Yi Gallery, 1991-1992 (Box 25)
  - Yo Kohama Musuem, 1988 (Box 25)
  - Yu, Jung Hee (Abraham), 1998 (Box 25)
  - Zylberstein, Jean-Claude, 1988-1991 (Box 25)
  - Zurich Art Fair, 1984-1993 (Box 25)
- Artists' Files, circa 1975-2002; Series 4; (Boxes 26-47; 22.0 linear feet)
  The artists' files include correspondence to and from the gallery about the artist in regards to their works, in particular the sales and payment information of works, shipping records and any insurance claims. Any correspondence between the gallery and the artist is also included in these files. Additional materials found here include printed materials, slides, photographs, clippings, and scattered inventory cards. There is substantial documentation on artists Kim MacConnel, Nam June Paik, Izhar Patkin, William Wegman, and Joe Zucker. Researchers should note that additional documentation on artists may also be found throughout this collection, especially within Series 3: Subject Files, Series 5: Inventory Records, Series 9: Printed Material, and Series 10: Photographic Materials.
  Files are in alphabetical order by artists' last name.
  - Acconci, Vito, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Africano, Nicholas, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Alveng, Dag, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Anderson, Laurie, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - ArtCurial, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Aythens, Olive, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Bark, Jared, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Barry, Robert, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Boetti, Alighiero, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Blatter, Camelia, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Brainard, Joe, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Carson, Neke, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Chamberlain, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Choi, Jae-Eun, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Christo, circa 1975-2002 (Box 26)
  - Christo, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Coach, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Consagra, Pier, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Davis, Brad, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Dennis, Donna, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - de Kooning, Willem, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Dietman, Erik, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Di Robilant, Tristano, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Drexler, Rosalyn, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Drooker, Eric, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Dufy, Raoul, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Eigenheer, Marianne, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Esta Correspondence, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Etkin, Suzan, circa 1975-2002 (Box 27)
  - Etkin, Suzan, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Fontana, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Galan, Julio, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Garabedian, Charles, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Garrin, Paul, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Gates Gallery, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - H.O. Gerngross Company, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Girouard, Tina, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Grover, Kit, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Graham, Susan, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Hakola, Marikki, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Hall, Susan, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Heilmann, Mary, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Hirst, Damien, circa 1975-2002 (Box 28)
  - Hoke, Lisa, circa 1975-2002 (Box 29)
  - Holland, Tom, circa 1975-2002 (Box 29)
  - Howland, Rebecca, circa 1975-2002 (Box 29)
  - Hurksman, Rini, circa 1975-2002 (Box 29)
  - Huebler, Douglas, circa 1975-2002 (Box 29)
  - Hutchinson, Peter, circa 1975-2002 (Box 29)
  - Ida, Shoichi, circa 1975-2002 (Box 29)
  - Incandela, circa 1975-2002 (Box 29)
  - Jacquette, Julia, circa 1975-2002 (Box 30)
  - Jaffe, Shirley, circa 1975-2002 (Box 30)
  - Jaudon, Valerie, circa 1975-2002 (Box 30)
  - Jenney, Neil, circa 1975-2002 (Box 30)
  - Jimenez, Elisa, circa 1975-2002 (Box 30)
  - Jimenez, Elisa, circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Johnson, Ray, circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Jones, Jerry, circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Kami, Y. Z., circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Kazuro, circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Kiefer, Anslem, circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Kilgore, Scott, circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Kirili, Alain, circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Kopystainsky, Igor, circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Kopystainsky, Svetlana, circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Kozloff, Max, circa 1975-2002 (Box 31)
  - Kozloff, Max, circa 1975-2002 (Box 32)
  - Richard Kuhlenschmidt Gallery, circa 1975-2002 (Box 32)
  - Kushner, Robert, circa 1975-2002 (Box 32)
  - Kuzuko, circa 1975-2002 (Box 32)
  - Lanigan-Schmidt, Thomas, circa 1975-2002 (Box 32)
  - Lanigan-Schmidt, Thomas, circa 1975-2002 (Box 33)
  - Lauder, Evelyn, circa 1975-2002; (See also box 19) (Box 33)
  - Lowe, Jean, circa 1975-2002 (Box 33)
  - MacConnel, Kim, circa 1975-2002 (Box 34)
  - Majore, Frank, circa 1975-2002 (Box 35)
  - Matta-Clark, Gordon, circa 1975-2002 (Box 35)
  - Matta-Clark, Gordon, circa 1975-2002 (Box 36)
  - Marti, Virgil, circa 1975-2002 (Box 36)
  - McCail, Chad, circa 1975-2002 (Box 36)
  - McCormick, Kelly, circa 1975-2002 (Box 36)
  - McDonough, Michael, circa 1975-2002 (Box 36)
  - Melchert, Jim, circa 1975-2002 (Box 36)
  - Mengbo, Feng, circa 1975-2002 (Box 36)
  - Mengbo, Feng, circa 1975-2002 (Box 37)
  - Meyer, Melissa, circa 1975-2002 (Box 37)
  - Miller, Melissa, circa 1975-2002 (Box 37)
  - Miraldi, circa 1975-2002 (Box 37)
  - Natz, Helga, circa 1975-2002 (Box 37)
  - Neshat, Shirin, circa 1975-2002 (Box 37)
  - Oppenheim, Dennis, circa 1975-2002 (Box 37)
  - Paik, Nam June, circa 1975-2002 (Box 38)
  - Paik, Nam June, circa 1975-2002 (Box 39)
  - Paik, Nam June, circa 1975-2002; (3 Binders) (Box 40)
  - Paik, Nam June, circa 1975-2002 (Box 41)
  - Patkin, Izhar, circa 1975-2002 (Box 41)
  - Patkin, Izhar, circa 1975-2002 (Box 42)
  - Pfaff, Judy, circa 1975-2002 (Box 42)
  - Pierson, Jack, circa 1975-2002 (Box 42)
  - Pitt, Suzan, circa 1975-2002 (Box 42)
  - Pollack, Barbara, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Polunin, Olga, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Pozzi, Lucio, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Provisor, Janis, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Rady, Elsa, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Rei Chek, Elaine, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Ripps, Rodney, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Rokeby, David, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Roversi, Paulo, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Rush, Cecily, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Scharf, Kenny, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Shostak, Ed, circa 1975-2002 (Box 43)
  - Shostak, Ed, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Slyce, John, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Smith, Lee, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Smyth, Ned, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Stikas, Marianne, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Stimm, Thomas, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Sweet, Paula, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Thurman, Blair, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Tuttle, Richard, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Waplington, Nick, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Warhol, Andy, circa 1975-2002 (Box 44)
  - Warhol, Andy, circa 1975-2002 (Box 45)
  - Weegee, circa 1975-2002 (Box 45)
  - Wegman, William, circa 1975-2002 (Box 45)
  - Wegman, William, circa 1975-2002 (Box 46)
  - West, David, circa 1975-2002 (Box 46)
  - Wynne, Rob, circa 1975-2002 (Box 46)
  - Xin, Yin, circa 1975-2002 (Box 46)
  - Zigmund, Almond, circa 1975-2002 (Box 46)
  - Zucker, Joe, circa 1975-2002 (Box 47)
- Inventory Records, 1975-2001; Series 5; (Boxes 48-66, 157-162; 25.0 linear feet)
  This series contains various inventory lists created by Holly Solomon Gallery as well as an art inventory card file. Inventory cards note the title, date, and size of the work as well as the dates and movements of the work. Some cards also include a Polaroid of the work of art. Researchers should note that scattered inventory cards may also be housed in Series 4: Artists' Files. The inventory cards span the life of the gallery, from 1975 to 2000. Inventory lists include print outs of the gallery inventory, logs kept to track works by artist, gallery checklists and stocklists, inventory lists for Holly Solomon Editions as well as inventories of Holly Solomon's personal collection.
  The inventory cards are arranged alphabetical by artist's last name. Within an artist grouping the cards are in order by accession number.
  - Card File: Acconci, Vito, 1985-1999 (Box 48)
  - Card File: Africano, Nicholas, 1979-1999; (10 folders) (Box 48)
  - Card File: Africano, Nicholas, 1979-1999; (9 folders) (Box 49)
  - Card File: Alveng, Dag, 1993-2000 (Box 49)
  - Card File: Anderson, Laurie, 1975-1993 (Box 49)
  - Card File: Anzinger, Siefried, 1984 (Box 49)
  - Card File: Artschwager, Richard, 1981-1994 (Box 49)
  - Card File: A Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 49)
  - Card File: Bark, Jared, 1975-1983; (2 folders) (Box 50)
  - Card File: Barry, Robert, 1988-2000; (2 folders) (Box 50)
  - Card File: Baxter, Glen, 1985-1999 (Box 50)
  - Card File: Blanchard, Remi, 1982-1990 (Box 50)
  - Card File: Blatter, Cornelia, 1988 (Box 50)
  - Card File: Boetti, Alighiero, 1990-1998 (Box 50)
  - Card File: Boogaard, Bert, 1989-1990 (Box 50)
  - Card File: Boisrand, Francois, 1982-1985 (Box 50)
  - Card File: Bowman, John, 1984-1990; (3 folders) (Box 50)
  - Card File: Brainard, Joe, 1981-1984 (Box 50)
  - Card File: Brathwaite, Fred, 1985-1987 (Box 50)
  - Card File: Burnley, Gary, 1979-1992; (2 folders) (Box 50)
  - Card File: Burson, Nancy, 1987-1989 (Box 50)
  - Card File: B Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 50)
  - Card File: Cady, Sam, 1975-1994; (2 folders) (Box 51)
  - Card File: Caldarelli, Biagio, 1990-1991 (Box 51)
  - Card File: Carlson, Mary, 1994-1995 (Box 51)
  - Card File: Carson, Neke, 1999 (Box 51)
  - Card File: Christo, 1981-1987 (Box 51)
  - Card File: Cohen, Cora, 1988-1990 (Box 51)
  - Card File: Combas, Robert, 1982-1985 (Box 51)
  - Card File: Connelly, Arch, 1985-1990 (Box 51)
  - Card File: Consagra, Pier, 1997-1999 (Box 51)
  - Card File: C Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 51)
  - Card File: Davis, Brad, 1975-1994; (4 folders) (Box 51)
  - Card File: Davis/Smyth (Brad Davis/Ned Smyth), 1982-1984 (Box 51)
  - Card File: Dennis, Donna, 1980-2000; (3 folders) (Box 52)
  - Card File: Di Robilant, Tristano, 1993-1997; (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - Card File: Di Rosa, Merve, 1982-1985 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Downing, Glenn, 1994-1995 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Drooker, Eric, 1996 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Dufy, Raoul, 1983-1990 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Dunning, Brad, 1989 (Box 52)
  - Card File: D Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Egleston, Truman, 1990-1992 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Eigenheer, Marianne, 1987-1999 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Etkin, Suzan, 1994-1999; (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - Card File: E Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Feng, Mengbo, 1997-1999 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Friedman, Dan, 1985-1987 (Box 52)
  - Card File: F Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Gallo, Doreen, 1985-1987 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Garouste, Gerard, 1982-1990 (Box 52)
  - Card File: Garrin, Paul, 1996-1999 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Girouard, Tina, 1975-1984; (2 folders) (Box 53)
  - Card File: Gonzalez, Michael, 1988-1990 (Box 53)
  - Card File: G Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Haas, Michel, 1983-1988 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Hall, Susan, 1981-1984 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Harris, Suzanne, 1981-1992 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Hatfield, John, 1994 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Hockelmann, Antonius, 1985 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Hoke, Lisa, 1999-2000 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Hockney, David, 1984-1988 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Horst, 1989-1990; (2 folders) (Box 53)
  - Card File: Howland, Rebecca, 1994-1997 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Huebler, Douglas, 1999-2000 (Box 53)
  - Card File: Hutchinson, Peter, 1981-1999; (4 folders) (Box 53)
  - Card File: Hutchinson, Peter, 1981-1999; (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Card File: H Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 54)
  - Card File: Ida, Shoichi, 1990-1991 (Box 54)
  - Card File: Indiana, Robert, 1981-1990 (Box 54)
  - Card File: Jacquette, Julia, 1995-1999 (Box 54)
  - Card File: Jaffe, Shirley, 1988-1995 (Box 54)
  - Card File: Jaudon, Valerie, 1976-1999; (3 folders) (Box 54)
  - Card File: Jenkins, Kiely, 1985-1986 (Box 54)
  - Card File: Jenney, Neil, 1970-1992 (Box 54)
  - Card File: Jimenez, Elisa, 1997-2000; (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Card File: Jones, Jerry, 1976-1990 (Box 54)
  - Card File: J Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 54)
  - Card File: Kami, Y. Z., 1995-1998; (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Card File: Kempinger, Herwig, 1991-1992 (Box 55)
  - Card File: Kilgour, Scott, 1986-1987 (Box 55)
  - Card File: Knowles, Christoper, 1977-1986; (2 folders) (Box 55)
  - Card File: Kopytiansky, Igor, 1997-1998 (Box 55)
  - Card File: Kopytiansky, Svetlana, 1997-1998 (Box 55)
  - Card File: Kunc, Milan, 1982-1988 (Box 55)
  - Card File: Kushner, Robert, 1975-2000; (10 folders) (Box 55)
  - Card File: Kushner, Robert, 1975-2000; (11 folders) (Box 56)
  - Card File: Kushner, Robert, 1975-2000; (13 folders) (Box 57)
  - Card File: K Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 57)
  - Card File: Lanigan-Schmidt, Thomas, 1975-1999; (12 folders) (Box 58)
  - Card File: Lewitt, Sol, 1995-1996 (Box 59)
  - Card File: Lichtenstein, Roy, 1981-1991 (Box 59)
  - Card File: Lowe, Jean, 1995-1998 (Box 59)
  - Card File: L Miscellaneous, circa 1975-2000 (Box 59)
  - Card File: MacConnel, Kim, 1981-1984 (Box 59)
  - Card File: MacConnel, Kim, 1981-1984 (Box 157)
  - Card File: MacConnel, Kim, 1981-1984 (Box 158)
  - Card File: Majore, Frank, 1990-1994 (Box 59)
  - Card File: Majore, Frank, 1990-1994 (Box 158)
  - Card File: Mapplethorpe, Robert, 1988-1992 (Box 59)
  - Card File: Margolies, John, 1988 (Box 59)
  - Card File: Marti, Virgil, 1998-1999 (Box 59)
  - Card File: Matta-Clark, Gordon, 1981-1984 (Box 59)
  - Card File: McCormick, Kelly, 1999 (Box 59)
  - Card File: Melchert, Jim, 1991 (Box 59)
  - Card File: Messager, Annette, 1982 (Box 59)
  - Card File: Meyer, Melissa, 1990-1998; (7 folders) (Box 59)
  - Card File: Meyer, Melissa, 1990-1998; (4 folders) (Box 60)
  - Card File: Miller, Melissa, 1983-1995; (2 folders) (Box 60)
  - Card File: Milloff, Mark, 1981-1990 (Box 60)